Kevin, you speak English? Okay. From the
beginning of the show until now, you
haven't smiled even
once. She forced you to come, isn't she?
You didn't want to come. You're married.
Yeah. Yeah. What's your name? Mara.
Nick, come by
yourself. She's so cool. Look how
beautiful. She's smiling. She's
laughing. How do you wake up next to
Kevin every morning? Good morning,
honey.
[Applause]
Kevin, that was funny. That was
funny. It's comedy. We're
joking. Kevin's like, "I'm going to sue
you after the
show. I'll show you."
I love you, Kevin. Ah, you smiling now.
You're
smiling. I look at
you. After the show, let's hang out. Me
and you, we'll go to a strip club.
Okay. Like, no problem. Just take him
away.
Brian. Brian. And you're married to an
Iranian? No. No. You uh you're here by
yourself? You you're here? Oh, you're
dating an Iranian. Okay. You don't need
to be an [\h__\h] about
it. Yeah. Nobody's
a cheeks don't need to
vibrate. You seem like a fun guy. You
got a great attitude. I like that. What
you do? Psychology. psychologist. Oh,
she needs
you. You guys are made in
heaven. I really hope it works out. And
what do you do?
I'm a genius. You're a
genius. You definitely need a
psychologist, honey.
See, in the history of all geniuses in
the world, they've never themselves
said, "I am genius."
See, other people identify who's a
genius. Brian, what do you think? Huh?
She is a genius. She is a genius. You
You just trying to get laid, but the
thing is the truth
is you don't introduce yourself as a
genius. I'm sure she's a genius. Yeah.
But socially even geniuses are genius
enough to know that you don't say that I
am genius because they're such geniuses
that they know that [\h__\h] is not okay to
say. See, it's a genius thing to do. Not
to say I'm
genius. I don't know how to explain
this. And and and what kind of genius?
Like in what format you're a
genius? Ryan, don't help her.
I'm working for Apple. You work for
Apple? Okay. Okay. Relax. We don't know
what she's
doing. Calm
down. Maybe she's customer. What can I
do for you?
Okay. Thank you for calling
Apple. Oh, is that the Okay, turn off
your phone. Turn it
on. Oh, it didn't work. Let me give you
to the engineer. Let me guess the [\h__\h]
she does. Let me find out what she does
for
[Applause]
Apple. This guy came with
sunglasses, buddy. Now you're in the
theater, huh?
Prescription. Prescription. What kind of
prescription they gave you? That's for
inside, but it's dark. So, the vision
gets better, but the color doesn't let
you see.
That's [\h__\h] to the nth
degree. Yep. Prescription, money.
Prescription.
Uh, what did what did you ask the
doctor? I asked to look
cool. They prescribed the coolness for
me. The point is you're stylish. That's
all that matters. Yeah. You see, better
with it or without it?
With it. A stick up a liar's ass.
Yeah. Do I want to see the doctor
prescribe it to you, not for me?
Nice start to the show.
[Applause]
[Music]
Okay, that was not a question. That was
a word that you just said,
huh? She doesn't know about the Where's
she from? What's your name? Hara.
From South Africa. Oh, you're beautiful.
What are you doing with this [\h__\h]
Are you dating him? Second date. Second
date. Wow.
Natasha, I want you to know something.
Yeah. He's bad
news. I'm not just saying it. This show,
I promise you this. This show, all of
these seats, maybe minus the very top
couple of rows, was sold out over a
month ago. Yeah, I'm not kidding. So, he
bought two
tickets. You will not The seat belongs
to someone else and he messed it up. And
listen, don't interrupt my
show. Don't interrupt my show, player,
cuz this is going to be your last date
tonight. Oh, and I'm going to explain
what Dooa
is. And Natasha is going to be my date
tonight.
Natasha, I'm going to fly you with
Everest Airlines back to Los
Angeles. So, this guy grew up thinking
he's got a golden
dick. And on a second date, he wanted me
to say, "Oh, this guy Golden Dick.
Please my
show. Please let them have a lucky
night." I shouldn't do that. I'm not an
[\h__\h] I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't
do that. I wouldn't do that. I wouldn't
do that. I wouldn't. We will meet
tomorrow, Natasha.
[Music]
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. This
seat is not
available. Sit there. Sit there. Okay.
Right there is fine. You're adorable.
So, wait a minute. I asked if anybody's
sitting here and you said no. No, no.
Uh, so I lost my father last year. Where
do I go?
A.
Oh, that's so
sweet. First of all, much blessing to
your father. And what's your name?
Retika. Retika. Retica. Where you from?
India. Indian. Okay. Wonderful to meet
you. I believe also when they say when
somebody passes away, they're always
with you. Yeah. And uh
I'm lost my father in
2015. And uh I would never do that.
You know
why? Because if I did that, my father's
soul would be so
unhappy. I'm telling you, my father be
like, "Maxin, why are you wasting
money? I am in
heaven having a great
time. What did I teach
you? You go up to be an idiot. You buy
seat for me.
stupid. I am in heaven having a good
time.
I don't even want to hang out with you.
Finally, I died to be away from you
guys. Now you're forcing me from heaven
to come watch this
[\h__\h] Hold on one second. Hold on.
Did you hear
that? I just heard your father
laugh. What a funny guy. I don't care.
I'd like to come sit next to my daughter
and watch your show.
Max to the
[Applause]
heavens
Junah.
[Applause]
Wow. So, what's the relationships? Yeah,
you two are together. Yeah. Where are
you
from? Go on. Russia. Russian. Look, he's
already sensitive. Bro, bring it. I [\h__\h]
you up.
I will destroy you from here to Russia.
Mother [\h__\h] bring your self to me.
Come to
daddy. Nice. What do you do in London?
I kill
people. I walk around. I don't like you.
you. I don't care. Don't like the way
you look. [\h__\h]
you. I'm Alex the
assassin. What is it? You a teacher?
Too. Nice, dude. What do you teach? How
to kill people.
Anybody here just came from Iran? Like
moved here to UK recently from Iran?
Yes. How long? Okay. Six weeks. Yeah.
You moved here for a good six weeks ago
and and your English is good. You came
here to see the
show. Yeah. It's okay. You understand?
That's wonderful, buddy.
Do you really understand?
Cuz I said, "Do you understand?" And
then you pause and you Googled, "What
is
[Applause]
yeah, please give it up for Miss Ali in
the house, the tech champion of
Iran. Thank you.
This is
amazing. I didn't know you're this tall.
My god. Of course you're a champion.
You're just like
[\h__\h] before the person gets into the
mat and you already knocked them
out. Ali, carry me. Send me a message. A
very sweet message.
and he's one of the best soccer players
that came out of the Middle East and on
top of that he became one of the biggest
advocates of Iran and he's he's an
incredible person that stands up for
humanity. He's a huge he's got a huge
heart. Anyways, he messaged me and he
said Kea in is she's in London and and I
I was so flattered that you're going to
come to the show. Uh, I was about to
roast you, but then I realized you're
the most dangerous person in the
audience to
roast Kim. She's she's world champion
over here, you know. It's
amazing.
Unbelievable. That's
awesome. And the guy next to
you, coach, you coach her.
Kima, you're so
talented. If this is the guy who coached
you and you won, [\h__\h] man. You're
natural
talent. You let this guy teach
you,
dude. Go to the gym at
least. What kind of Tekwondo coach wears
glasses?
Sorry, I kicked your ass. One second.
[Applause]
Buddy, stand up. Everybody, meet the
coach. Yeah. Stand up.
Everybody after the show. I kick your
[Applause]
ass. Thank you. So, you're also a
martial artist. Yeah. You're also a
Tekwondo champion. Awesome, buddy. Thank
you. This is This is pride and joy for
us. Yeah. This is like when you say,
"Tell us something special about Iran."
Right here. She's
[Applause]
here. I had people from Malovia
yesterday, people from Croatia. It was
really fun. And tonight seems like a
nice mix as well. Yeah. You didn't play.
Where are you from? I'm from London.
You're from London. Nobody's from
London.
Why are you acting like this? No, you're
not. Have you looked at yourself in the
mirror?
Go to the airport. Let me see where you
from. Go to the airport. Who the hell
are
you? You think these white people look
at you and they go, "She's one of
us."
No.
Instead, it's true.
Instead, they whisper to each other,
"Oh, you see that girl? She different
color." I'm like, "Oh, you one of us."
Okay. Hi. Hey,
cheers. You don't want to tell me your
ethnicity? From Bangladesh. Bangladesh.
You said, "Where are you
from? You're from Bangladesh. Bangladesh
is a beautiful country. Everybody should
be so proud of where they're from, their
ancestors, their parents, that's when
you
realize you have
[Music]
identity. Yeah. If you don't own it and
own it and you don't learn about it, my
parents are from Bangladesh. That means
you don't know [\h__\h] about
Bangladesh. It's a fascinating country.
Yeah. Where are you from? None of your
goddamn business.
I am American.
His comedy is writing itself.
Who kind of grew up here? Anybody? Yeah.
How old are you? 75. You're 75. Wow.
Congratulations. You look beautiful.
Yeah. And how many years you've been in
the in the UK? I came when I was nine.
That's incredible. Wow. What's your
name? Fish. Ferish it. You kept it.
Mom, you're so cool. I can't see you. Do
you mind just coming closer? Cuz she's
visually impaired. She even has her
binoculars and she can't see any of your
face. That's it. She cannot see. She's
asking me to go closer because she
brought binoculars. Mom, this is a
comedy show.
I know she told you she's taking to a
show of a guy called Gul
Talo and you think if I get closer to
you, you will see some
gold. But to be honest, I'm fully
clothed right
now. And the closer I get, the worse
it's going to look. I'd rather you just
imagine me as the doodle tala and not
have to see anything more.
What made you leave from Iran and come
to the UK? My parents were very
forwardthinking and they didn't have
boys. So me and my sister came over to
England to be educated. I'm very happy
you're here. And because you can't see
me, I'll come to
you. Enjoy. Enjoy your show.
66 years in the UK. Both of them smell
like
onion. You guys had some kina before the
show. Just
kidding. You smell amazing. I love you
so much. Thank you for being here. We
learned so much tonight. I got to do
this fast. I'm I'm taking the time and
and the the second show is coming. Huh?
Up here. Up here. Do what?
You want to kiss?
She thinks it's free.
No, honey.
You pay VIP, you get cheese.
Holland. That's a beautiful part of the
Middle
East.
Algeria. Wow. Wow, nice to see you. I've
never had anyone ever in 22 years of
doing comedy at my show from
Algeria. I am so impressed you're here.
I'm so happy, habibi, you showed up
because Algerians are busy doing
terrorist [\h__\h] all the
time. Please don't blow up the building.
Okay, I love you. I'm totally kidding.
We're all terrorists.
[Music]
In what? So what? Let me
see. Fridge. I can't I can't [\h__\h]
read, dude. Open the goddamn so I can
read it.
I sell fridges. Okay, show it to
everybody. It's like you were prepared
for this [\h__\h]
I got you four years ago. How? What do
you really do? What's your thing?
You working? Selfages.
Self what? Selfages.
Selfages. I don't understand you.
Selfages. This accent is crazy. It was
nice talking to
you. Thanks for the annunciating.
You sell
perfume. I mean, you got a very edgy
look. The last thing I thought you being
the most smells amazing. Would you like
to smell this
moan? You're so freaking
sensitive. You're such a
wuss. Four years later, you buy front
row
tickets, buy a t-shirt. My self
vision, you are the epitome of a doodle.
[Music]